spanishprograms.com 2010-01-13

# Visual Link Spanish(TM) Privacy Policy

The U.S. Institute of Languages ("USIL") Privacy Policy- This privacy policy affects www.spanishprograms.com("Site") 

USIL has established this privacy policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your personal information. We intend to provide protection for your personal information no matter where that personal information is collected, transferred, or retained. By using any of the above Site's services you agree that you understand the policy set forth in this document and agree to be bound to the terms stated. If you disagree with this policy you must discontinue use of all Sites as listed above. Also, please note that USIL is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-USIL Web Sites to which this Site or any other USIL Web Site may link. You should review the privacy policy of such Sites before using the Sites. 

**Personal Information** \--   
Personal information is defined as any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work, at home, or otherwise. 

**Children** \--   
If a child under the age of 13 desires to access parts of the Site that require personal information to be given, the child must have their parents set up an account on their behalf. 

**Use of Personal Information** \--   
As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as subscribing to the collaboration services offered on the Site or utilizing online software applications, USIL may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, USIL may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, and other personal information. When ordering products or services on the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. This information will be secured to the best of our abilities. Using industry standard SSL encryption and residing on secure servers. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. Once you register and sign-in you are no longer anonymous to USIL. 

**Updating your personal information** \--   
You may also access and correct your personal information by writing or calling USIL at: 

U.S. Institute of Languages   
Attn: Customer Relations   
4699 S. Harrison Blvd Suite 200   
South Ogden, UT 84403   
USA 

Telephone number 866-977-2647 

Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us. In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site where you provided your personal information. 

**Security of Personal Information** \--   
Wherever your Personal Information may be held within USIL or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the personal information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Some areas of the Site use industry standard SSL while in others information is password and username protected. We will also limit access to such information to employees who reasonably need access to such information to complete their jobs. Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room is available to all persons accessing that location. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@spanishprograms.com. We take every reasonable action to protect your privacy, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible. 

**Sharing of Personal Information** \--   
USIL does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except under the following circumstances: 

* We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.   
* We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of USIL's terms of service, or as otherwise required by law.   
* Like many companies that accept payment by credit card, USIL may share customers' personal information with qualified third parties in order to process your order or perform a credit worthiness check. 

**Technological Tracking** \--   
Some of our web pages use "cookies"(a cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.) or other technological tracking devices. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, and the Internet Protocol ("IP") address of your computer. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web Site and your Web experience. USIL may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. USIL may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information. 

**Communications** \--   
Users cannot opt-out of receiving administrative communications related to their accounts. Such e-mail may include confirmation of a registration or purchase or communication during the sales or support process. E-mail communications from us, such as our weekly newsletters are opt-in and opt-out. Other communications, such as after you buy a product are used to follow up, and are on a strict opt-out basis. You will not receive any "spam" or any correspondence of a questionable nature from us. We only use the e-mail addresses to send periodic notes regarding updates, additions, sales, or other beneficial information that pertains to this webSite or our company. USIL is a family oriented company and we will always make sure that any correspondence that you may receive from us is appropriate for any age. 

**Inquires** \--   
USIL takes its users' privacy concerns seriously, and will take every reasonable action to protect your privacy. If you believe that USIL has not complied with this online privacy policy with respect to your personal information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write to the USIL customer relations at the address indicated above. In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which you believe that the USIL online privacy policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your inquiry or complaint promptly.   
**  
Changes to Privacy Policy** \--   
USIL reserves the right to change the privacy policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. If as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which USIL is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described above in the section titled "Updating your personal information." You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days.
